Why didn't you use the door?
لماذا لم تستخدم الباب؟
Climbing through windows is dangerous.
التسلق عبر النوافذ أمر خطير.
If we're putting on an act, we should go all the way.
إذا كنا نرغب في تمثيل شيء ما، فيجب علينا أن نستمر حتى النهاية.
So we don't waste
حتى لا نضيع
Mr. Mu's good intentions.
نوايا السيد مو الطيبة.
But tell me,
ولكن قل لي
did they believe it?
هل صدقوا ذلك؟
You said
أنت قلت
it was an award-winning performance.
لقد كان أداءً حائزًا على جائزة.
They must have believed it.
لا بد أنهم صدقوا ذلك.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What exactly happened?
ماذا حدث بالضبط؟
It was all arranged by Gu Xiaomeng.
لقد تم ترتيب كل هذا بواسطة Gu Xiaomeng.
He must have found out
لابد أنه اكتشف ذلك
that I'm investigating the truth about that accident.
إنني أتحقق من حقيقة هذا الحادث.
Guilty conscience, I guess.
ضمير مذنب، على ما أعتقد.
I figured as much.
لقد اعتقدت ذلك.
That's why I'm pretending to be paralyzed,
لهذا السبب أتظاهر بأنني مشلول،
to make them lower their guard
لجعلهم يخفضون حذرهم
while I search for evidence.
بينما أبحث عن الأدلة.
But it's been so many years.
ولكن لقد مرت سنوات عديدة.
It might be difficult to find anything.
قد يكون من الصعب العثور على أي شيء.
The Gu siblings have always been arrogant.
لقد كان الأشقاء جو متغطرسين دائمًا.
They wouldn't have covered their tracks completely.
لم يكونوا ليتمكنوا من إخفاء آثارهم بشكل كامل.
There must be some clues left behind.
لا بد من أن يكون هناك بعض الأدلة التي تركت وراءها.
I believe
انا أؤمن
the spirits of my brother and sister-in-law
أرواح أخي وزوجة أخي
will surely protect me.
سوف يحميني بالتأكيد.
So you've learned to use your charm now.
لقد تعلمت الآن كيفية استخدام سحرك.
Yes.
نعم.
After all my sacrifices,
بعد كل تضحياتي،
how do you plan to make it up to me?
كيف تخطط لتعويضي؟
Sis.
أخت.
Are you really bringing Mu Qiushan over?
هل ستحضرين حقا مو تشيوشان؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you upset?
هل انت منزعج؟
No,
لا،
I just think there's more to him.
أعتقد فقط أن هناك المزيد عنه.
His leg injury might be fake.
ربما تكون إصابة ساقه مزيفة.
It's precisely because he's not that simple
إنه على وجه التحديد لأنه ليس بهذه البساطة
that we need to keep him where we can watch him.
أننا بحاجة إلى إبقائه في مكان يمكننا مراقبته.
That's a good idea.
هذه فكرة جيدة.
Find a way to get
ابحث عن طريقة للحصول عليها
the patent as soon as possible.
براءة الاختراع في أقرب وقت ممكن.
After you arrive at the Gu family,
بعد وصولك إلى عائلة جو،
you must be careful.
يجب عليك أن تكون حذرا.
Gu Nian isn't stupid,
قو نيان ليس غبيًا،
she won't be easy to deal with.
لن يكون من السهل التعامل معها.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
If you don't enter the tiger's den,
إذا لم تدخل عرين النمر،
how can you catch the cubs?
كيف يمكنك اصطياد الأشبال؟
At least you're still working behind the scenes.
على الأقل أنك لا تزال تعمل خلف الكواليس.
We'll coordinate from inside and outside,
سنقوم بالتنسيق من الداخل والخارج،
and stay in touch.
والبقاء على اتصال.
I'm leaving then.
سأغادر إذن.
Be careful.
احرص.
This is really nice.
هذا جميل حقا.
Thank you for your trouble.
شكرا على تعبك.
No need to be polite.
لا داعي لأن تكون مهذبا.
We'll be family soon.
سوف نكون عائلة قريبا.
Xiaomeng,
شياو مينج،
hurry up and pour tea for your brother-in-law.
اسرعي واسكبي الشاي لصهرك.
Qiushan,
كيوشان،
are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Are you hurt?
هل انت مصاب؟
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
Luckily they're just useless legs.
لحسن الحظ أنهم مجرد أرجل عديمة الفائدة.
Xiaomeng,
شياو مينج،
what's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
You can't even pour water properly.
لا يمكنك حتى صب الماء بشكل صحيح.
Apologize to your brother-in-law right now.
اعتذر لشقيق زوجك الآن.
Ever since Mu Qiushan came to the Gu family,
منذ أن جاء مو تشيوشان إلى عائلة جو،
my sister has been giving me the cold shoulder
لقد كانت أختي تتجاهلني
and treating me with contempt.
ومعاملتي بازدراء.
You can't stand the sight of me, right?
لا يمكنك تحمل رؤيتي، أليس كذلك؟
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
You.
أنت.
Qiushan.
كيوشان.
Don't be angry with Xiaomeng.
لا تغضب من شياومينغ.
He just has a strange temper.
إنه لديه مزاج غريب.
I'll go talk to him.
سأذهب للتحدث معه.
Okay.
تمام.
It seems Mu Qiushan's legs
يبدو أن ساقي مو تشيوشان
are truly crippled.
لقد أصيبوا بالشلل حقا.
His legs are ruined.
ساقيه مدمرة.
My heart isn't dead yet.
قلبي لم يمت بعد
How dare you lie to me.
كيف تجرؤ على الكذب علي؟
Then don't blame me for being ruthless.
إذن لا تلوموني على كوني قاسيًا.
What are you planning to do, sis?
ماذا تخططين للقيام به يا أختي؟
Isn't Mu Qiushan investigating the sports car incident?
أليس مو تشيوشان يحقق في حادثة السيارة الرياضية؟
He'll never find any evidence.
لن يجد أي دليل أبدًا.
At this moment
في هذه اللحظة
we can take the opportunity.
يمكننا أن نستغل الفرصة.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
Oh no, sis.
أوه لا، نعم.
Mu Qiushan seems to have discovered
يبدو أن مو تشيوشان قد اكتشف
that the car was mine.
أن السيارة كانت لي.
This is all your fault.
كل هذا خطؤك .
Go after him now!
إذهب خلفه الآن!
When you catch him,
عندما تمسك به،
break his legs.
كسر ساقيه.
We've already bought the wheelchair,
لقد اشترينا بالفعل الكرسي المتحرك،
might as well put it to use.
قد يكون من الأفضل استخدامه.
Get in the car.
ادخل إلى السيارة.
Hurry!
عجل!
Stop!
قف!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Nian.
لنا.
Xiaomeng is so capable,
شياو منغ قادر جدًا،
he'll definitely catch Mu Qiushan.
سوف يمسك مو تشيوشان بالتأكيد.
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
Even if we don't catch him,
حتى لو لم نتمكن من القبض عليه،
I have other ways.
لدي طرق أخرى.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
He got away.
لقد هرب.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Fang Yue has
لقد فعل فانغ يو
already found where the patent documents are hidden.
تم العثور بالفعل على المكان الذي يتم فيه إخفاء وثائق براءات الاختراع.
While Mu Qiushan
بينما مو كيوشان
and Jiang Chunyu are still figuring things out,
وما زال جيانغ تشونيو يحاولان فهم الأمور،
let's go get those documents back first.
دعونا نذهب للحصول على تلك الوثائق أولاً.
Get them back.
استرجعهم .
Of course.
بالطبع.
Why do you think the old man
لماذا تعتقد أن الرجل العجوز
is so obsessed with this marriage alliance?
هل أنت مهووس بهذا التحالف الزواجي؟
It's not just because the Mu family has patents,
ليس فقط لأن عائلة مو لديها براءات اختراع،
but also because
ولكن أيضا لأنه
they have a mature R&D team.
لديهم فريق بحث وتطوير ناضج.
And a tech production line.
وخط إنتاج التكنولوجيا.
But
لكن
having patents alone
امتلاك براءات الاختراع وحدها
is useless.
لا فائدة منه.
Of course it's useful.
بالطبع إنه مفيد.
Once we have the patent documents,
بمجرد حصولنا على وثائق براءة الاختراع،
we can set up our own R&D and production team,
يمكننا إنشاء فريق البحث والتطوير والإنتاج الخاص بنا،
and it'll work just the same.
وسوف يعمل بنفس الطريقة.
What do you think those old guys on the board
ما رأيك في هؤلاء الرجال المسنين في المجلس؟
really want?
هل تريد حقا؟
Isn't this exactly what they're after?
أليس هذا بالضبط ما يبحثون عنه؟
Meng,
منغ،
thank you for your hard work today.
شكرا لك على عملك الجاد اليوم.
As for this matter,
أما في هذا الشأن،
I'll handle it myself.
سأتعامل مع الأمر بنفسي.
Meng.
منغ.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Of course he's stealing the patent documents for me.
بالطبع فهو يسرق وثائق براءة الاختراع مني.
Otherwise, for something so dangerous,
وإلا، لشيء خطير كهذا،
would he let me go?
هل سيسمح لي بالذهاب؟
Even if Mu Qiushan isn't home,
حتى لو لم يكن مو تشيوشان في المنزل،
there should still be a housekeeper.
لا يزال ينبغي أن يكون هناك مدبرة منزل.
Why is it so quiet?
لماذا هذا الهدوء؟
A trap.
فخ.
I only have one chance.
لدي فرصة واحدة فقط.
Whether it's a trap or not,
سواء كان فخًا أم لا،
I must get that patent.
يجب أن أحصل على تلك البراءة.
Your trick of drawing the snake out of its hole
حيلتك لإخراج الثعبان من جحره
really works well.
يعمل بشكل جيد حقا.
Luring Gu Nian to steal patents from the Mu family.
إغراء قو نيان لسرقة براءات الاختراع من عائلة مو.
She won't fall for it, will she?
إنها لن تصدق ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Even a cornered dog will leap over a wall.
حتى الكلب المحاصر سوف يقفز فوق الحائط.
She's left with nothing now.
لم يبق لها أي شيء الآن.
If there's even a 1% chance,
إذا كان هناك حتى 1٪ فرصة،
she'll take it.
ستأخذها.
Cut the crap.
إقطع الهراء.
If you've got the guts, take me to the police station.
إذا كان لديك الشجاعة، خذني إلى مركز الشرطة.
Taking you to the police station
أخذك إلى مركز الشرطة
would be letting you off too easy.
سيكون من السهل جدًا السماح لك بالخروج.
Ten years ago,
منذ عشر سنوات،
when you were driving that modified sports car,
عندما كنت تقود تلك السيارة الرياضية المعدلة،
did you hit someone?
هل ضربت أحدا؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Jiang Chunyu won't get away.
جيانغ تشونيو لن يهرب.
Brother.
أخ.
Yes, I have.
نعم لدي.
I've bumped into many people.
لقد التقيت بالعديد من الأشخاص.
Which one are you talking about?
عن أي واحد تتحدث؟
Let me see if I remember.
دعني أرى إذا كنت أتذكر.
You beast!
يا وحش!
Qiushan!
كيوشان!
Hit me!
ضربني!
Beat me to death!
اضربني حتى الموت!
Will that bring your brother and sister-in-law back to life?
هل سيؤدي ذلك إلى إرجاع أخيك وزوجة أخيك إلى الحياة؟